<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>WildFly Elytron</title>
        <link>https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron</link>
        <description></description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 17:30:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Open Source Day 2021 Recap</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/open-source-day-recap/
            </link>
            <description>
                A couple weeks ago, the WildFly Elytron team had a great time participating in Open Source Day, an all-day hackathon that took place during the virtual Grace Hopper Celebration (vGHC). This was the WildFly Elytron team&#8217;s second time participating in this event, after having been a part of the recent...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/open-source-day-recap/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Hacktoberfest Has Begun</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/hacktoberfest-has-begun/
            </link>
            <description>
                The WildFly Elytron project is participating in Hacktoberfest this month and welcomes your contributions! What is Hacktoberfest? Hacktoberfest takes places annually during the month of October. This event encourages open source contributions from the community. To participate in Hacktoberfest, you simply need to: Register on the Hacktoberfest site Submit 4...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/hacktoberfest-has-begun/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Open Source Day Summer 2021 Recap</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/open-source-day-summer-recap/
            </link>
            <description>
                Last week, the WildFly Elytron team had the pleasure of participating in Open Source Day, an all-day hackathon hosted by the AnitaB.org community. It was the very first time that this event, known as the largest female-led movement in open source, was held outside of the Grace Hopper conference. Participants...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/open-source-day-summer-recap/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Installing Keycloak OIDC adaptor using the Galleon CLI</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/galleon-cli-keycloak/
            </link>
            <description>
                Traditionally to install WildFly you would download a complete archive of the application server distribution, unzip it locally and run it directly from where it was unzipped. Subsequently to install the Keycloak adaptor for WildFly a second archive would be downloaded and unzipped on top of the WildFly installation and...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/galleon-cli-keycloak/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Using hash character sets and encodings in Elytron</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/hash-charsets-encodings/
            </link>
            <description>
                In the legacy security configuration using PicketBox, the UsernamePasswordLoginModule supports storing hashed passwords by specifying the hashing algorithm, encoding and character set to compare the client-supplied password to the password stored in the management system. Previously, Elytron supported specifying the hashing algorithm, but not the string encoding or character set...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/hash-charsets-encodings/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>SSLv2Hello with WildFly</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/oneway-sslv2hello/
            </link>
            <description>
                It is now possible to use SSLv2Hello with WildFly. This blog post will give an introduction to this new feature, but it will assume previous knowledge on how to configure SSL in Elytron. For more information on how to configure SSL, refer to the elytron documentation. An Overview of SSLv2Hello...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/oneway-sslv2hello/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>SSL Certificate Revocation Lists with WildFly</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/ssl-certificate-revocation-list/
            </link>
            <description>
                An Overview of Certificate Revocation Lists Configuring CRLs on the Client Side Back Up Your Standalone Server Configuration Pre-requisite Server Configuration Pre-requisite Client Configuration Configure the Server Create the Certificate Revocation Lists Configure a Client that verifies certificates against CRLs Build and Deploy the Application Run the Client and Verify...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/ssl-certificate-revocation-list/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Secure WildFly CLI with Keycloak</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/secure-wildfly-cli-with-keycloak/
            </link>
            <description>
                This blog post gives an example of how to secure WildFly CLI using Keycloak and Elytron. Keycloak&#8217;s Wildfly Elytron Adapter Download WildFly server, Keycloak server and the WildFly OpenID Connect client adapter for WildFly from keycloak.org. Make sure your versions are compatible. Then, extract the contents of the client adapter...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/secure-wildfly-cli-with-keycloak/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Invoking EJBs over HTTP</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/ejb-over-http/
            </link>
            <description>
                Server Configuration Prerequisite Configuration Configure the HTTP Transport Client Configuration Prerequisite Configuration Performing Invocations Summary The ejb-http quickstart will describe the steps to setting up EJBs using HTTP as the transport. It will also secure it with a FileSystem realm, and use a credential store to access the EJB. This...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/ejb-over-http/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>WildFly Encrypted Expression Support</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/wildfly-encrypted-expressions/
            </link>
            <description>
                With the release of WildFly 23 the WildFly Elytron project and it&#8217;s integration now adds support for encrypted expressions within the management model, this post will describe the steps to quickly get started using this new feature. Introduction The CredentialStore functionality provided by WildFly Elytron provides a mechanism for the...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/wildfly-encrypted-expressions/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
