<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>WildFly Elytron</title>
        <link>https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron</link>
        <description></description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 17:32:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>SSL Certificate Revocation Lists with WildFly</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/ssl-certificate-revocation-list/
            </link>
            <description>
                An Overview of Certificate Revocation Lists Configuring CRLs on the Client Side Back Up Your Standalone Server Configuration Pre-requisite Server Configuration Pre-requisite Client Configuration Configure the Server Create the Certificate Revocation Lists Configure a Client that verifies certificates against CRLs Build and Deploy the Application Run the Client and Verify...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/ssl-certificate-revocation-list/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Secure WildFly CLI with Keycloak</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/secure-wildfly-cli-with-keycloak/
            </link>
            <description>
                This blog post gives an example of how to secure WildFly CLI using Keycloak and Elytron. Keycloak&#8217;s Wildfly Elytron Adapter Download WildFly server, Keycloak server and the WildFly OpenID Connect client adapter for WildFly from keycloak.org. Make sure your versions are compatible. Then, extract the contents of the client adapter...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/secure-wildfly-cli-with-keycloak/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Invoking EJBs over HTTP</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/ejb-over-http/
            </link>
            <description>
                Server Configuration Prerequisite Configuration Configure the HTTP Transport Client Configuration Prerequisite Configuration Performing Invocations Summary The ejb-http quickstart will describe the steps to setting up EJBs using HTTP as the transport. It will also secure it with a FileSystem realm, and use a credential store to access the EJB. This...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/ejb-over-http/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>WildFly Encrypted Expression Support</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/wildfly-encrypted-expressions/
            </link>
            <description>
                With the release of WildFly 23 the WildFly Elytron project and it&#8217;s integration now adds support for encrypted expressions within the management model, this post will describe the steps to quickly get started using this new feature. Introduction The CredentialStore functionality provided by WildFly Elytron provides a mechanism for the...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/wildfly-encrypted-expressions/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Upcoming hash character sets and hash encodings support in Elytron</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/upcoming-hash-encodings/
            </link>
            <description>
                One of the features we have been working on for the Elytron subsytem is the ability to specify the hash character set and hash encoding in security realms that support storing hashed passwords. The purpose of this task is to ensure feature parity with legacy security configurations. We have plans...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/upcoming-hash-encodings/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Upcoming SSLContext that supports delegation to alternate instances based on peer information</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/sslcontext-delegation-to-alternate-instances-based-on-peer/
            </link>
            <description>
                One of the features we have been working on for the Elytron subsytem is the ability to configure SSL context that will delegate to different instances of SSL context based on the host and port of the peer. Background In some cases it can be useful to have SSL context...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/sslcontext-delegation-to-alternate-instances-based-on-peer/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Normalize principal propagation/injection across elytron and legacy</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/normalization-of-EJB-principal-propagation/
            </link>
            <description>
                In WildFly 23 there is a new configuration option in the EJB subsystem that allows to switch between legacy and elytron principal propagation. This blog post will provide an explanation about the difference between these propagation modes and where the configuration can be done. Definition of terms Secured EJB refers...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/normalization-of-EJB-principal-propagation/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Upcoming SSL features: Multiple certificate revocation lists support and SSLv2Hello support</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/new-ssl-features/
            </link>
            <description>
                Two of the new features regarding SSL that we have been working on include adding support for configuring multiple certificate revocation lists and SSLv2Hello support. These features did not make it into WildFly 23 but we have plans for them to be included in WildFly 24. An Overview of Certificate...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/new-ssl-features/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>New Security Features in WildFly 23</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/new-security-features-in-wildfly-23/
            </link>
            <description>
                This blog post highlights the new security features that are in WildFly 23 and also gives an update on the new security features that the Elytron team has been working on. New Features in WildFly 23 Encrypted Expression Support WildFly 23 now adds support for encrypted expressions within the management...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/new-security-features-in-wildfly-23/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Upcoming automatic registration of client side default SSLContext</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/automatic-registration-of-client-side-jvm-wide-default-sslcontext/
            </link>
            <description>
                One of the features we have been working on for the Elytron subsytem is the ability to automatically register client side JVM wide default SSL context. This SSL context will be available to any library that supports the use of the default context. Details We plan to provide implementation of...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/automatic-registration-of-client-side-jvm-wide-default-sslcontext/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
