<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>WildFly Elytron</title>
        <link>https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron</link>
        <description></description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:13:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Identity Propagation with OIDC</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/wildfly-oidc-identity-propagation/
            </link>
            <description>
                When securing an application with OpenID Connect (OIDC), WildFly automatically creates and makes use of a virtual security domain across the deployment. If the application invokes an EJB, additional configuration might be required in order to propagate the security identity from the virtual security domain. The configuration that&#8217;s needed depends...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/wildfly-oidc-identity-propagation/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Change the default encoding of the audit log file in WildFly 29</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/specify-file-audit-log-encoding/
            </link>
            <description>
                The default encoding used for the audit log file is UTF-8. You can change the default encoding by specifying encoding attribute in file-audit-log, periodic-rotating-file-audit-log or size-rotating-file-audit-log elements in the Elytron subsystem. Possible values are: UTF-8, UTF-16BE, UTF-16LE, UTF-16, US-ASCII or ISO-8859-1. &lt;file-audit-log name="local-file" path="audit.log" relative-to="jboss.server.log.dir" synchronized="false" autoflush="true" format="JSON" encoding="UTF-16"/&gt; ......
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/specify-file-audit-log-encoding/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Securing WildFly Apps with OIDC on OpenShift</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/securing-wildfly-apps-oidc-openshift/
            </link>
            <description>
                You can secure your WildFly applications deployed on OpenShift with OpenID Connect (OIDC). By using OIDC to secure applications, you delegate authentication to OIDC providers. This guide shows how to secure an example application deployed to WildFly on OpenShift with OIDC using Keycloak as the OIDC provider. Prerequisites Example Application...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/securing-wildfly-apps-oidc-openshift/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Adding Support for Integrity Checking to an Existing Filesystem Realm</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/filesystem-integrity-elytron-tool/
            </link>
            <description>
                WildFly 27 included the ability to add integrity checking support to filesystem realms. This uses an asymmetric key pair that has a private and public key to secure the filesystem realm. In the filesystem realm, each identity will be signed using the private key. This makes it possible to verify...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/filesystem-integrity-elytron-tool/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Open Source Day 2023 Recap</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/ghc23-osd-recap/
            </link>
            <description>
                Last month, the WildFly Elytron team had the great pleasure of participating in Open Source Day, an all-day hackathon that took place as part of the 2023 Grace Hopper Celebration. This was the fourth time that the WildFly Elytron team has participated in this event. It is always an exciting...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/ghc23-osd-recap/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Vlog: Join us at Open Source Day on September 22, 2023 and Make Meaningful Contributions</title>
            <link>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nevZyt2TkzI
            </link>
            <description>
                
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nevZyt2TkzI
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Vlog: Join us at Open Source Day and Level Up Your Skills</title>
            <link>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9i_MiK0W2n4
            </link>
            <description>
                
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9i_MiK0W2n4
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Securing WildFly Apps with SAML on OpenShift</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/securing-wildfly-apps-saml-openshift/
            </link>
            <description>
                Starting with WildFly 29, you can use Galleon to add Keycloak&#8217;s SAML adapter to your WildFly installation using the new Keycloak SAML Adapter feature pack. In this guide, we&#8217;ll show how to secure an application deployed to WildFly on OpenShift with SAML. Prerequisites Example Application Log Into the OpenShift Cluster...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/securing-wildfly-apps-saml-openshift/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Vlog: Join us at Open Source Day, No Prior Experience Needed</title>
            <link>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PAcqCa8u0Z8
            </link>
            <description>
                
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PAcqCa8u0Z8
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Vlog: Begin your Open Source Journey with the WildFly Elytron Project at Open Source Day</title>
            <link>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vUWGPTCNl4I
            </link>
            <description>
                
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vUWGPTCNl4I
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
