<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>WildFly Elytron</title>
        <link>https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron</link>
        <description></description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 14:41:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Upcoming filesystem realm encryption and integrity support in Elytron</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/upcoming-filesystem-encryption-integrity/
            </link>
            <description>
                Two features that we have been working during the WildFly 26 development phase is the ability to encrypt filesystem security realms with a SecretKey, and the ability to verify filesystem integrity with a KeyPair. This feature will be included in a future WildFly release. An Overview of Filesystem Realm Encryption...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/upcoming-filesystem-encryption-integrity/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Securing WildFly Apps with OpenID Connect</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/securing-wildfly-apps-openid-connect/
            </link>
            <description>
                WildFly 25 added the ability to secure applications using OpenID Connect, without needing to make use of the Keycloak client adapter. This blog post gives an introduction to this feature. OpenID Connect New elytron-oidc-client Subsystem Deployment Configuration Subsystem Configuration Required Configuration Options OpenID Providers Securing an application using OIDC Example...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/securing-wildfly-apps-openid-connect/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>New Security Features in WildFly</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/new-security-features-wildfly/
            </link>
            <description>
                Since WildFly 26 was just released, we wanted to highlight a new security feature included in this release and a few other security features as well. Support for JAAS Security Realms in WildFly 26 WildFly 26 now adds support for JAAS security realms to the Elytron subsystem. This means that...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/new-security-features-wildfly/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Using a JAAS realm in Elytron</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/jaas-realm/
            </link>
            <description>
                The Elytron subsystem already provides various security realms like LDAP realm, JDBC realm, filesystem realm, and others for common use cases. Starting from WildFly 26, you can also configure a JAAS security realm in the Elytron subsystem in order to use custom Login Modules for authentication and authorization. A JAAS...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/jaas-realm/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Upcoming client side default SSL context provider</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/client-side-jvm-wide-default-sslcontext/
            </link>
            <description>
                Currently it is possible to configure SSL contexts in the Elytron client configuration which can be used by interacting with the Elytron client and its APIs. In a future WildFly release, we will provide the ability to register a JVM wide default SSL context that other libraries can obtain without...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/client-side-jvm-wide-default-sslcontext/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Using failover realm in Elytron</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/failover-realm/
            </link>
            <description>
                With a failover realm you can configure an alternative realm that will be used if primary realm is not available. A common use case is to fail over to a local file based realm if an LDAP or database server has gone down allowing administrators to retain access to the...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/failover-realm/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Using distributed realm in Elytron</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/distributed-realm/
            </link>
            <description>
                With a distributed realm you can combine identities located across multiple security realms of any type into a single security realm. Identities can be used for both authentication and authorization purposes. Add a distributed realm You can add a distributed-realm to the Elytron subsystem by specifying the list of realms...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/distributed-realm/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Open Source Day 2021 Recap</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/open-source-day-recap/
            </link>
            <description>
                A couple weeks ago, the WildFly Elytron team had a great time participating in Open Source Day, an all-day hackathon that took place during the virtual Grace Hopper Celebration (vGHC). This was the WildFly Elytron team&#8217;s second time participating in this event, after having been a part of the recent...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/open-source-day-recap/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Hacktoberfest Has Begun</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/hacktoberfest-has-begun/
            </link>
            <description>
                The WildFly Elytron project is participating in Hacktoberfest this month and welcomes your contributions! What is Hacktoberfest? Hacktoberfest takes places annually during the month of October. This event encourages open source contributions from the community. To participate in Hacktoberfest, you simply need to: Register on the Hacktoberfest site Submit 4...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/hacktoberfest-has-begun/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Open Source Day Summer 2021 Recap</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/open-source-day-summer-recap/
            </link>
            <description>
                Last week, the WildFly Elytron team had the pleasure of participating in Open Source Day, an all-day hackathon hosted by the AnitaB.org community. It was the very first time that this event, known as the largest female-led movement in open source, was held outside of the Grace Hopper conference. Participants...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/open-source-day-summer-recap/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
