<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>WildFly Elytron</title>
        <link>https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron</link>
        <description>WildFly Elytron: Security, Authentication, and Authorization SPIs for the WildFly project</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 17:42:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Anomaly based Intrusion Detection System</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/anomaly-based-intrusion-detection-system/
            </link>
            <description>
                Intrusion Detection is the art of sensing when a system or network is being used inappropriately or without authorization. Without intrusion detection, an attacker can attempt attacks many times until an attack is finally successful. Intrusion detection allows for these attacks to be identified before a successful attack is likely...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/anomaly-based-intrusion-detection-system/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Introduction to Rule Engine & Blacklist IP Dump of Intrusion Detection System</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/introduction-rule-engine-and-blacklist-dump/
            </link>
            <description>
                Earlier we introduced Intrusion Detection System using Elytron&#8217;s security events and discussed its architecture. In this blog we&#8217;ll discuss the implementation of Rule Engine &amp; Blacklist IP Dump. Rule Engine Rule Engine comprises of a set of pre-defined rules, which are used to score the event on a scale of...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/introduction-rule-engine-and-blacklist-dump/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>An Introduction to Intrusion Detection System using Elytron</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/architectural-overview-intrusion-detection-system/
            </link>
            <description>
                Intrusion Detection is the art of sensing when a system or network is being used inappropriately or without authorization. Without intrusion detection, an attacker can attempt attacks many times until an attack is finally successful. Intrusion detection allows for these attacks to be identified before a successful attack is likely...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/architectural-overview-intrusion-detection-system/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Using regex role mapper in Elytron</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/regex-role-mapper/
            </link>
            <description>
                Elytron subsystem configuration was enhanced to allow possibility to define a regex based security roles mapping mechanism. With this functionality it is possible to easily translate list of roles, eg. app-admin, abc-user, to simpler roles , eg. admin, user. Add a regex role mapper You can add a regex-role-mapper to...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/regex-role-mapper/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Planned Security Features for WildFly</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/planned-security-features-for-wildfly-21/
            </link>
            <description>
                Since the feature development phase for WildFly 21 has now started, we wanted to highlight the new security features that we will be working on. Planned Features Security Realm Enhancements WFCORE-4485 Support for multiple security realms - Distributed Identities This new feature will make it possible to use multiple security...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/planned-security-features-for-wildfly-21/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Advanced EJB: Securing EJBs using a FileSystem realm and invoking them from a remote client using a credential store</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/advanced-ejb-security/
            </link>
            <description>
                The ejb-security quickstart demonstrates an advanced example on how to secure EJBs using a FileSystem realm with SCRAM-SHA-512 SASL authentication along with a client credential store. The focus is on the Elytron configuration, so if you wish to learn more about using Jakarta EE declarative security to control access to...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/advanced-ejb-security/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Using the IP Address of a Remote Client for Authorization Decisions</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/using-remote-client-ip-for-authorization/
            </link>
            <description>
                WildFly 20 adds the ability to make use of the IP address of a remote client when making authorization decisions. This blog post will give an overview of this new feature. Authorization Decisions Roles and permissions can be assigned to a security identity based on attributes that are loaded from...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/using-remote-client-ip-for-authorization/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Automatic Credential Store Updates</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/automatic-credential-store-updates/
            </link>
            <description>
                WildFly 20 adds support for automatic credential store updates. This blog post will give an overview of this new feature. Credential Stores Credential stores allow credentials to be stored securely. When adding a credential to a store, it is associated with an alias. This alias is then subsequently used to...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/automatic-credential-store-updates/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Elytron's ACME Client Implementation</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/elytron-acme-client-implementation/
            </link>
            <description>
                The Automated Certificate Management Environment (ACME) protocol became an IETF standard a little over a year ago. This protocol makes it possible to automate the process of obtaining signed certificates from a certificate authority without the need for human intervention. The WildFly Elytron project provides a Java ACME client SPI...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/elytron-acme-client-implementation/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Server Side SNI Matching with WildFly</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/server-side-sni-matching-with-wildfly/
            </link>
            <description>
                For quite some time now, WildFly has provided support for server side Server Name Indication (SNI) matching. This allows a WildFly instance with multiple virtual hosts that share a single IP address to present the correct certificate depending on the server name specified by the client via the SNI extension....
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/server-side-sni-matching-with-wildfly/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
