<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>WildFly Elytron</title>
        <link>https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron</link>
        <description></description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 15:25:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Vlog: Join us at Open Source Day, No Prior Experience Needed</title>
            <link>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PAcqCa8u0Z8
            </link>
            <description>
                
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PAcqCa8u0Z8
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Vlog: Begin your Open Source Journey with the WildFly Elytron Project at Open Source Day</title>
            <link>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vUWGPTCNl4I
            </link>
            <description>
                
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vUWGPTCNl4I
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Securing the WildFly Management Console with OpenID Connect</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/securing-management-console-oidc/
            </link>
            <description>
                WildFly 29 Final, which was just released last week, includes the ability to secure the WildFly Management Console with OpenID Connect using the Keycloak OpenID provider. This blog post gives an overview of how to configure this. OpenID Connect Securing the WildFly Management Console with the Keycloak OpenID Provider Keycloak...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/securing-management-console-oidc/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Using Certificate Based Authentication with Mutual TLS without Roles</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/Client-cert-auth-without-roles/
            </link>
            <description>
                Mutual TLS with client certificates is essential for secure and encrypted communication between clients and servers in various applications and systems. It involves a handshake process during which both the client and the server must present their certificate to each other in order to establish a secure connection. This ensures...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/Client-cert-auth-without-roles/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Configuring the Digest mechanism to make use of additional algorithms</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/specify-http-digest-algorithms/
            </link>
            <description>
                The default algorithm used for the digest authentication mechanism is MD5. You can configure the WildFly server to also require or accept the SHA-256 and SHA-512-256 algorithms. This configuration can be specified in the mechanism-configuration attribute of both the http-authentication-factory and the sasl-authentication-factory: &lt;http-authentication-factory name="exampleHttpAuthFactory" security-domain="exampleSD" http-server-mechanism-factory="global"&gt; &lt;mechanism-configuration&gt; &lt;mechanism mechanism-name="DIGEST-SHA-256"&gt;...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/specify-http-digest-algorithms/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Using Custom Principals with Elytron</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/using-custom-principals-with-elytron/
            </link>
            <description>
                Sometimes, you need to access additional information about an authenticated user. As an example, you may want to know when they logged in, or what information they have on file. Traditionally, this type of information needed to be stored using security realm attributes associated with an identity. Now in WildFly...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/using-custom-principals-with-elytron/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>AMA Recap</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/ask-me-anything-recap/
            </link>
            <description>
                The WildFly Elytron team had our very first Ask Me Anything (AMA) session on chat this week. Thanks very much to those who joined! This blog post gives a recap of the session in case you missed it. Q: How can I contribute to Elytron as a person who has...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/ask-me-anything-recap/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Ask Me Anything with the WildFly Elytron Team</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/ask-me-anything/
            </link>
            <description>
                The WildFly Elytron team will be having an Ask Me Anything (AMA) session on Monday Dec. 19th on chat. This is your chance to ask any questions about: Contributing to the WildFly Elytron project How to use WildFly Elytron General questions about contributing to open source projects The AMA session...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/ask-me-anything/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Vlog: Filesystem Realm Integrity</title>
            <link>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tzd9GTr8kwE
            </link>
            <description>
                
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tzd9GTr8kwE
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Vlog: Git Tips on Upstream Repositories and Merge Conflicts</title>
            <link>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v5d6x3kT7lU
            </link>
            <description>
                
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v5d6x3kT7lU
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
