<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>WildFly Elytron</title>
        <link>https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron</link>
        <description></description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 15:21:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Open Source Day 2022 Recap</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/ghc22-open-source-day-recap/
            </link>
            <description>
                Last month, the WildFly Elytron team had the great pleasure of participating in Open Source Day, an all-day hackathon that took place as a pre-event before the 2022 Grace Hopper Celebration. This was the WildFly Elytron team&#8217;s third time participating in this event, after having participated in the Summer Open...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/ghc22-open-source-day-recap/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Hacktoberfest Has Started</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/hacktoberfest/
            </link>
            <description>
                
            </description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/hacktoberfest/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>FAQ for New Contributors</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/frequently-asked-questions-new-contributors/
            </link>
            <description>
                It&#8217;s very common for new contributors to any project to have questions on how to get started. In this post, we thought we&#8217;d capture some frequently asked questions we&#8217;ve received from new contributors to the WildFly Elytron project. How do I find an issue to work on? How do I...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/frequently-asked-questions-new-contributors/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Bearer Token Support for the Elytron OIDC Client Subsystem</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/bearer-only-support-openid-connect/
            </link>
            <description>
                WildFly 26.1.2.Final, which was just released, includes the ability to secure applications with bearer tokens when using the Elytron OpenID Connect (OIDC) Client subsystem. This blog post gives an overview of how to configure applications deployed to WildFly so they can support Bearer Token Authentication. Bearer Token Authentication Securing an...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/bearer-only-support-openid-connect/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Top 5 Reasons To Join Us At Open Source Day</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/top-five-reasons-to-join-elytron-open-source-day/
            </link>
            <description>
                Last month, we were thrilled to announce that the WildFly Elytron project was selected for Open Source Day, an all-day hackathon hosted by AnitaB.org as part of the Grace Hopper Celebration. This is our third time taking part in this event, after having participated in the Summer Open Source Day...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/top-five-reasons-to-join-elytron-open-source-day/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Vlog: Encrypting a Filesystem Realm</title>
            <link>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1K92tit2uCk
            </link>
            <description>
                
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1K92tit2uCk
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Securing Jakarta Enterprise Beans with mutual TLS authentication</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/ejb-over-tls/
            </link>
            <description>
                The ejb-mutual-tls example demonstrates how to use Elytron to secure EJBs with mutual TLS authentication. It also shows how to restrict access to EJBs, configuring a FileSystem realm protected by SASL authentication, and accessed using a credential store. This example focuses on the TLS configuration, so if you wish to...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/ejb-over-tls/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>New Security Features in WildFly 26.1</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/new-security-features-wildfly-26-1/
            </link>
            <description>
                Since WildFly 26.1 was just released, we wanted to highlight some new security features included in this release. New Features Automatic Registration of a Client Side Default SSLContext The Elytron authentication client now provides a Java security provider that can be used to register a JVM wide default SSLContext. When...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/new-security-features-wildfly-26-1/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Improving readability of certificate read commands</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/improving-readability-of-alias-commands/
            </link>
            <description>
                Any one who has experience with network hardware or console administration knows the Achilles' heel of CLI - limited visualization capability. This can be somewhat mitigated by setting large horizontal buffer and simple scrolling. However not all devices support scrolling and output still can be loitered with wrapped lines. This...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/improving-readability-of-alias-commands/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Encrypting Filesystem realms</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/filesystem-encryption/
            </link>
            <description>
                Previously, any data in the filesystem realm was always stored unencrypted, this meant that anyone with access to the filesystem identity files could access the credentials, and attributes (such as assigned roles). Now encryption has been added via a SecretKey. An overview of the new attributes The filesystem realm now...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/filesystem-encryption/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
