<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

    <channel>
        <title>WildFly Elytron</title>
        <link>https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron</link>
        <description></description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 20:37:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
            <title>Trying Out An Upcoming Security Feature for WildFly on OpenShift</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/in-progress-wildfly-feature-on-openshift/
            </link>
            <description>
                A future release of WildFly will include the ability to add additional scope values when securing applications using OpenID Connect (OIDC). This blog post demonstrates how to secure a WildFly application using OpenID Connect and configure scope values to request additional claims using an in-progress version of the feature. This...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/in-progress-wildfly-feature-on-openshift/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Vlog: Securing WildFly Apps with Okta on OpenShift</title>
            <link>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=usquALvL2qc
            </link>
            <description>
                
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=usquALvL2qc
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Securing WildFly Applications Using Okta on OpenShift</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/securing-wildfly-apps-okta-openshift/
            </link>
            <description>
                WildFly applications can be secured using OpenID Connect and deployed to OpenShift. By using OIDC to secure applications, you delegate authentication to OIDC providers. The elytron-oidc-client subsystem can be used to secure an application deployed to WildFly using any OpenID Provider. This guide demonstrates how to secure an example application...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/securing-wildfly-apps-okta-openshift/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Vlog: Securing WildFly Apps with Auth0 on OpenShift</title>
            <link>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uoQoCPGyAik
            </link>
            <description>
                
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uoQoCPGyAik
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Securing WildFly Apps with Auth0 on OpenShift</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/securing-wildfly-apps-auth0-openshift/
            </link>
            <description>
                You can secure your WildFly applications deployed on OpenShift with OpenID Connect (OIDC). By using OIDC to secure applications, you delegate authentication to OIDC providers. This guide shows how to secure an example application deployed to WildFly on OpenShift with OIDC using Auth0 as the OIDC provider. If you prefer...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/securing-wildfly-apps-auth0-openshift/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Using distributed realm ignore-unavailable-realms attribute in Elytron</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/distributed-realm-ignore-unavailable-realms/
            </link>
            <description>
                A distributed-realm is made up of a list of realms. Each realm in the list is sequentially attempted until we either find the user or run out of realms. If a realm happens to be unavailable, by default search is stopped altogether. With the introduction of the ignore-unavailable-realms boolean attribute...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/distributed-realm-ignore-unavailable-realms/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Identity Propagation with OpenID Connect</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/wildfly-oidc-identity-propagation/
            </link>
            <description>
                When securing an application with OpenID Connect (OIDC), WildFly automatically creates and makes use of a virtual security domain across the deployment. If the application invokes an EJB, additional configuration might be required in order to propagate the security identity from the virtual security domain. The configuration that&#8217;s needed depends...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/wildfly-oidc-identity-propagation/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Change the default encoding of the audit log file in WildFly</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/specify-file-audit-log-encoding/
            </link>
            <description>
                The default encoding used for the audit log file is UTF-8. Starting from WildFly 29, you can change the default encoding by specifying encoding attribute in file-audit-log, periodic-rotating-file-audit-log or size-rotating-file-audit-log elements in the Elytron subsystem. Possible values are: UTF-8, UTF-16BE, UTF-16LE, UTF-16, US-ASCII or ISO-8859-1. &lt;file-audit-log name="local-file" path="audit.log" relative-to="jboss.server.log.dir" synchronized="false"...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/specify-file-audit-log-encoding/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Securing WildFly Apps with OIDC on OpenShift</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/securing-wildfly-apps-oidc-openshift/
            </link>
            <description>
                You can secure your WildFly applications deployed on OpenShift with OpenID Connect (OIDC). By using OIDC to secure applications, you delegate authentication to OIDC providers. This guide shows how to secure an example application deployed to WildFly on OpenShift with OIDC using Keycloak as the OIDC provider. Prerequisites Example Application...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/securing-wildfly-apps-oidc-openshift/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Adding Support for Integrity Checking to an Existing Filesystem Realm</title>
            <link>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/filesystem-integrity-elytron-tool/
            </link>
            <description>
                WildFly 27 included the ability to add integrity checking support to filesystem realms. This uses an asymmetric key pair that has a private and public key to secure the filesystem realm. In the filesystem realm, each identity will be signed using the private key. This makes it possible to verify...
            </description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            <guid>
                https://wildfly-security.github.io/wildfly-elytron/blog/filesystem-integrity-elytron-tool/
            </guid>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
